A Guide to the Papers of Alice Jackson Stuart, 1913-2001
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Notes and Writings by Alice Jackson Stuart (Box 20)
  - Notes concerning Use of Television and Radio in Education n.d. (Box 26)
  - Notes concerning Troy Legend from Homer to Dryden at Columbia University (2 folders) 1937 (Box 26)
  - Notebooks concerning Black History and Culture and Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 26)
  - Notebook concerning Black History and Culture and Poverty n.d. (Box 26)
  - Notebook, possibly of the talks given at the First Unitarian Society of Plainfield n.d. (Box 26)
  - Notebook concerning Human Relations Issues in Education (4 folders) ca. 1952-1965 (Box 27)
  - Notebook concerning Teaching and Education 1959-1962, n.d. (Box 27)
  - Note Cards - Black Americans n.d. (Box 27)
  - Note Cards - Black Americans n.d. (Box 28)
  - Note Cards - Black History and Literature n.d. (Box 28)
  - Note Cards - Black Women n.d. (Box 28)
  - Note Cards - Books and Articles n.d. (Box 28)
  - Note Cards - Films, Filmstrips, Television and Sound Recordings n.d. (Box 28)
  - Note Cards - Marriage, Family, and Values n.d. (Box 28)
  - Note Cards - Miscellaneous Topics n.d. (Box 28)
  - Note Cards - Don Newcombe Biography (2 folders) ca. 1965 (Box 29)
  - Note Cards - Quotations n.d. (Box 29)
  - Note Cards - Teaching (2 folders) n.d. (Box 29)
  - Play Script "L'Arrabiata (The Spitfire) by Paul Heyser Adaptation for Television by Alice Jackson Houston ca. 1954 (Box 29)
  - Play Script Notes n.d. (Box 29)
  - Poetry (2 folders) ca. 1951-1955 (Box 30)
  - "Programs for the Disadvantaged" Workshop II, National Council of Teachers of English 1967 Apr 21-22 (Box 30)
  - "Proposal for Using Multiple Instructional Devices in Teaching English" by Alice Jackson Stuart n.d. (Box 30)
  - "Recognizing Speech Faults and Defects" n.d. (Box 30)
  - Short Stories 1964, n.d. (Box 30)
  - "Some Observations on Station KTHE Educational Television" ca. 1953 (Box 30)
  - Speech for Middlesex County College Senior Investiture 1975 May 7 (Box 30)
  - Talks and Speeches by Alice Jackson Stuart 1962, n.d. (Box 30)
  - University of Virginia - Speech at the Office of Afro-American Affairs Honors Banquet 1990 (Box 30)
  - Virginia News and Reviews 1955 (Box 30)
- Series IV: Subject & Topical Files (Box 30)
  - American Association of Community and Junior Colleges - Journals 1970-1975 (Box 30)
  - American Association of University Women 1960-1970 (Box 30)
  - "American Baptist Home Mission Society and Hartshorn Memorial College: Their Missions and Influences on Education for Negro Women" by Carmen Foster 1998 Dec 17 (Box 30)
  - American Foundation for Negro Affairs 1968 (Box 30)
  - American Friends Service Committee - Lima, Ohio Work Camp 1949, 1994 (Box 31)
  - American Kennel Club 1975-1978 (Box 31)
  - Art, Design, and Fashion ca. 1964-1967 (Box 31)
  - Arts - Artists 1966-1997 (Box 31)
  - Arts - Art and Literature Correspondence 1971-1999 (Box 31)
  - Arts - Literature 1966-1992 (Box 31)
  - Arts - Miscellaneous Art Work n.d. (Box 31)
  - Arts - Richmond Symphony 1982, 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - Arts - Swain Art Store 1979-1986 (Box 31)
  - Arts - Theater 1967-2001 (Box 31)
  - Arts - Thirteen 1977-1998 (Box 31)
  - Association for the Study of Afro-American Life and History 1976-1999 (Box 31)
  - Association of Black Women in Higher Education 1981-1987 (Box 31)
  - The Berkshire 1993-2000 (Box 31)
  - Bernards High School, Bernardsville, New Jersey 1954-1955 (Box 31)
  - Mary McLeod Bethune 1949-1975 (Box 31)
  - Mary McLeod Bethune - Poster of United States Black Heritage Stamp (oversize) n.y. Feb 26 (Box 31)
  - Bethune-Cookman College, Daytona Beach, Florida 1940-1985 (Box 31)
  - Black Athletes 1973-1999 (Box 32)
  - Blacks in Business 1949-1997 (Box 32)
  - Black English 1965-1977 (Box 32)
  - Black Family Genealogies 1982-1991 (Box 32)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center of Virginia 1989-2000, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Black Poets and Authors (2 folders) 1965-1998, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Black Studies 1958-1998, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Black Women (2 folders) 1973-2001, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Cazenovia, New York Black Studies Conference 1968 (Box 33)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions 1962-1964 (Box 33)
  - Children's Literature 1954-1991 (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights (2 folders) 1958-2001, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights - Legislative Bills 1963 (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights - Martin Luther King, Jr. 1964-1989 (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - American Association for Affirmative Action 1987 (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - Common Cause 1974-1994 (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - Equal Opportunities/Civil Rights Bulletin/Student Voice 1962-1973 (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - Herbert Lehman Education Fund 1969-1982 (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored Persons (NAACP) 1962-1990 (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored Persons (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund (2 folders) 1965-1999, n.d. (Box 34)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored Persons (NAACP) Special Contribution Fund 1966-1999 (Box 34)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - National Urban League 1949-1980 (Box 34)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - Southern Poverty Law Center 1973-1999 (Box 34)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - Southern Poverty Law Center - Teaching Tolerance 1990-2000 (Box 34)
  - Civil Rights Organizations - United Negro College Fund 1961-2000 (Box 34)
  - Cloning 1978-1979, n.d. (Box 34)
  - College English - Miscellaneous Newsletters 1967-1980 (Box 34)
  - College Language Association 1974-1994 (Box 34)
  - College Language Association 1995-2000, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Colleges 1966-1996, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Columbia University 1937-2001 (Box 35)
  - Columbia University Teachers College Courses concerning Educational Radio and Television (2 folders) 1947-1952 (Box 35)
  - The Concord Coalition 1992-1993 (Box 35)
  - Conference for Secondary School English Department Chairmen - Newsletters 1974-1982 (Box 35)
  - Conference on International Education 1979 (Box 35)
  - Coordinating Council on Human Rights 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Council for a Television Course in the Humanities for Secondary Schools, Inc. 1959 (Box 35)
  - Angela Davis Case 1970-1971 (Box 35)
  - Professor Arthur P. Davis 1955-1992 (Box 35)
  - Dictionary of Literary Biography Afro-American Writers 1981-1984 (Box 35)
  - Dolls for Democracy - Guidelines and Story Scripts n.d. (Box 36)
  - Douglas College 1957-1969, n.d. (Box 36)
  - Educational Broadcasting - WNYE, New York City 1955 (Box 36)
  - Educational Problems and Issues 1958-1989, n.d. (Box 36)
  - Emancipation Proclamation Centennial Observance 1962-1963 (Box 36)
  - Equal Rights Amendment 1995 (Box 36)
  - Ethnicity in Language and Literature 1970-1976 (Box 36)
  - Evanston Township High School, Evanston, Illinois - English Sequential Programs 1959 (Box 36)
  - Examinations and Bibliographies concerning Literature 1945-1946 (Box 36)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University Writers Workshop 1964 (Box 36)
  - First Unitarian Church of Richmond 1957-2000, n.d. (Box 36)
  - First Unitarian Church of Richmond - Bulletins 1961-2000 (Box 37)
  - First Unitarian Society of Plainfield, N.J. and First Unitarian Church of Plainfield 1956-1970 (Box 37)
  - Ford Foundation 1953, 1978, 1980 (Box 37)
  - Catherine Foster at University of Virginia 1993 (Box 37)
  - Harlem Education Program, Inc. Prospectus 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - "Harlem on My Mind: Cultural Capital of Black America 1900-1968 Poets and Heroes" - Postcard Set of Photographs ca. 1968 (Box 37)
  - Hartshorn Memorial College, Richmond, Virginia 1929-1979 (Box 37)
  - Harvard University, W. E. B. DuBois Institute 1981-1983 (Box 37)
  - Health Care - King-Anderson Bill 1961-1962 (Box 37)
  - High School English - Miscellaneous Bulletins 1956-1966 (Box 37)
  - Housing and Urban Renewal 1961, 1973 (Box 37)
  - Housing and Urban Renewal 1949-1973 (Box 38)
  - Howard University 1965-1997 (Box 38)
  - Howard University - English Examinations 1939-1963 (Box 38)
  - Howard University - Post card Scenes n.d. (Box 38)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs 1980-1983 (Box 38)
  - Institute for Children's Literature 1985-1987, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Johnson Publishing Company - Jet Newsletter 1955-1956, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Lois Mailou Jones 1983-1987 (Box 38)
  - Kilmer Job Corps Center, Edison, New Jersey (3 folders) 1965-1966, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Kilmer Job Corps Center, Edison, New Jersey Newsletter "The Kilmer Era" 1966 (Box 38)
  - Kilmer Job Corps Center, Edison, New Jersey - Photographs 1945-[1965] (Box 38)
  - Kilmer Job Corps Center, Edison, New Jersey - Suggested Curriculum for the Study of Language by Jack Taub n.d. (Box 39)
  - Koinona 1972-1983 (Box 39)
  - The Langston Hughes Society 1981-2000 (Box 39)
  - William Wendell Layton and Family 1978-1998, n.d. (Box 39)
  - Hylan Lewis 1955-2000 (Box 39)
  - Library of Virginia/Virginia State Library 1990-2000 (Box 39)
  - MacLeish Symposium 1982 (Box 39)
  - Midcentury White House Conference on Children and Youth 1950 Dec 3-7 (Box 39)
  - Middle-Atlantic Writers Association 1981 (Box 39)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey (2 folders) 1966-1970 (Box 39)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey (3 folders) 1971-1999, n.d. (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Application for Sabbatical Leave 1975-1982 (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Catalogs 1969-1972 (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Campus Telephone Directories and Handbook 1970-1980 (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Commencements 1968-1981 (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Contracts 1976-1982 (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Flux Literary Magazine 1967-1973 (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "FYI For Your Information" Newsletter 1999-2000 (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Foundation, Inc. 1970-2000 (Box 40)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Learning Resource Center 1968-1971, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Library and Media Center 1968, 1970, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" - Prospectus, Course Outline, and Bibliography 1969-1980 (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Abolitionists 1970-1971, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Abolitionists - Frederick Douglass 1970-1971, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Athletes 1971, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Authors 1970-1972, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Authors - James Baldwin 1970-1972, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Authors - Ralph Ellison 1970-1973 (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Authors - Langston Hughes 1970-1971, n.d. (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Authors - Claude McKay 1970-1981 (Box 41)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Black Leaders and Historical Figures 1971-1972, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Black Organizations and Founders 1971-1972, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning the Black Press 1970, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Cultural Issues and Society 1971-1974, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Drama and Theater 1971-1972, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning History 1971-1980, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Music 1969-1974, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Political 1971, 1976, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Religion 1971, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Literature of Black America" Student Papers concerning Nat Turner and other Slave Revolts, and Riots 1968-1973, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Proposal for Individualizing Instruction in the Humanities, Composition, and Communication Courses 1967 (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Programs 1971-1982 (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Reports of the President and Others 1965-1981 (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Report by Middle States Commission on Institutions of Higher Learning 1968 (Box 42)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - "Second Extension of the Campus Master Plan 1972-1982" 1972 (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Student Film and Other Reviews 1968-1977, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Student Papers 1971-1980, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Student Papers by Virginia French 1976 (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Student Poetry 1972, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Teaching Evaluations of Alice Jackson Stuart and other Personnel Actions 1975-1981, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Teaching Evaluations of Alice Jackson Stuart by Students 1975 (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Teaching Evaluations of the Course "Literature of Black America" (taught by Alice Jackson Stuart) by Students (3 folders) 1970-1974, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County College, Edison, New Jersey - Yearbook 1980 (Box 43)
  - Middlesex County Cultural and Heritage Commission 1979, 1981 (Box 44)
  - Morristown High School, Morristown, New Jersey - Curriculum of the English Department 1962 (Box 44)
  - Museums - Miscellaneous 1952-2000, n.d. (Box 44)
  - Museums - New Jersey 1969-1987 (Box 44)
  - Museums - New York City - Miscellaneous 1968-2001, n.d. (Box 44)
  - Museums - Smithsonian, National Gallery, Washington, D.C. 1989-2000, n.d. (Box 44)
  - National Center for Urban Partnerships, Richmond Meeting (1994) 1994 Jun 9-11 (Box 44)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc. 1953-1964 (Box 44)
  - National Council of Teachers of English (NCTE) 2 folders 1952-1995, n.d. (Box 44)
  - National Council of Teachers of English [Annual Convention?], including notes concerning Boston Meeting 1952, 1954 (Box 44)
  - National Council of Teachers of English Annual Convention, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania 1973 (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English Annual Convention, Boston, Massachusetts 1981 (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English Annual Convention, Washington, D.C. 1982 (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English affiliate newsletter 1973-1976 (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Directories 1967, 1974 (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Printed (2 folders) 1959-1981 (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication 1966-1986, n.d. (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Annual Meeting (2 folders) 1968-1993 (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Manual for Workshop Leaders 1963, n.d. (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Conference on English in the Two-year Junior College - By-laws and Membership Lists 1965, 1969-1971 (Box 45)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College - Correspondence (3 folders) 1965-1969 (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Executive Committee 1972-1974, n.d. (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College - Rhode Island Junior College, Providence, RI (1967) 1967 (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College - Adirondack Community College, Glen Falls, NY (1968) 1968 (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College - Community College of Philadelphia (1969) and Boston University (1970) 1969-1970 (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College - Prince George's Community College, Largo, MD (1971) 1971 (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College - Queensborough Community College, New York City (1972) and [Pittsburgh, PA?] 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College, Philadelphia, PA (1976) 1976 (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College - Boston, MA (1982) 1982 (Box 46)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication - Northeast Regional Meeting on English in the Two-year Junior College - Newsletters Ca. 1969-1982 (Box 47)
  - National Council of Teachers of English - Conference on College Composition and Communication Task Force "Student's Right to Their Own Language" 1972-1974 (Box 47)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities 1981-1983, n.d. (Box 47)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities - Application 1981 (Box 47)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities - Correspondence 1967-1987 (Box 47)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities - Yale Summer Seminar and Afro-American Cultural Center 1981-1988 (Box 47)
  - New Jersey Association of Teachers of English 1963-1968 (Box 47)
  - New Jersey Council of Teachers of English 1975, n.d. (Box 47)
  - New Jersey Higher Education Report 1969 (Box 47)
  - New Jersey Teachers for Integrated Quality Education 1963-1964, n.d. (Box 47)
  - Newark Community School 1967 (Box 47)
  - News clippings 1965-1999, n.d. (Box 47)
  - The Niagara Movement Commemoration at Harper's Ferry, West Virginia 1996 (Box 47)
  - Organizations - American Friends Service Committee 1956-1998, n.d. (Box 47)
  - Organizations - Children's Defense Fund 1983-1999, n.d. (Box 48)
  - Organizations - Miscellaneous, including: American Association for the Advancement of Humanities, American Civil Liberties Union, Black Silent Majority Committee, Carter Center, Congress of Racial Equality, Covenant House, Fellowship of Reconciliation, Guidance Association of Pleasantville NY, Medgar Evers Fund, Moral Majority, National Black Pastor's Conference, National Service Corps, National Sharecroppers Fund, Negroes for a Constitutional Campaign Victory, New York Urban League, People for the American Way, President's Committee on Mental Retardation, Scholarship Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality, Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund, Southern Christian Leadership Conference, Southern Development Foundation, Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, Students for a Democratic Society, UNICEF 1953-1997, n.d. (Box 48)
  - Organizations - Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority 1981-1988, n.d. (Box 48)
  - People - Isaiah Jackson 1969-1987, n.d. (Box 48)
  - People - Jesse Jackson 1990, n.d. (Box 48)
  - People - Clara B. Jones 1998-1999 (Box 48)
  - People - News clippings 1967-1999, n.d. (Box 48)
  - People - Price Family 1988-1989 (Box 48)
  - People - Resumes, Contemporary Biography 1956-2002, n.d. (Box 48)
  - People - Pauline A. Young 1982-1983 (Box 48)
  - Piscataway Township High School Department of English 1961-1962 (Box 48)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey (2 folders) 1952-1974, n.d. (Box 48)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - The Community Service Council Inc. 1962-1965 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Education and Community Issues 1960-1972 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Elizabeth and Plainfield Urban Educational Centers 1975-1976 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Housing Authority 1962-1976 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Housing Authority Dedication Ceremonies for Richmond Towers 1974 May 11 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Housing Authority Richmond Towers Project 1969-1974, n.d. (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Madison Park Project 1961-1972 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Madison Park Project - Final Report 1961 Apr (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Master Plan (oversize) 1959 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Public Schools 1962-1983 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Mayor Richard L. Taylor 1974-1985 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - Cornelia Ward 1989-1996 (Box 49)
  - Plainfield, New Jersey - "The West End Survey" 1960 May (Box 50)
  - Play Typescript "God is a N[ ----- ] A Morality Play with Music" by Ray McIver n.d. (Box 50)
  - Play Typescript "Mayhem at Mayhew" by David S. Meranze and Marc Alan Zagoren 1971 (Box 50)
  - Play Typescripts for three one-act plays "Study in Color" by the Rev. Malcolm Boyd 1960-1962 (Box 50)
  - Play Typescripts from the National Conference of Christians and Jews n.d. (Box 50)
  - Political Issues - Communism 1962 (Box 50)
  - Political Organizations - Campaign Literature McGovern for President 1972 (Box 50)
  - Political Organizations - Democratic Party (3 folders) 1961-2000, n.d. (Box 50)
  - Political Organizations - Democratic Party Prints and Photographs 1963-1997 (Box 50)
  - Political Organizations - The Virginia State Legislative Black Caucus 1995-1997 (Box 50)
  - Politics - Candidates (2 folders) 1966-2000, n.d. (Box 51)
  - Politics - John F. Kennedy 1960-2001 (Box 51)
  - Politics - Party Issues 1953-1996, n.d. (Box 51)
  - Politics - Party Issues and Reform 1962-1999 (Box 51)
  - Poverty 1965-1967 (Box 51)
  - Quotations re Books and Reading 1950-1961, n.d. (Box 51)
  - Racism 1963-1999, n.d. (Box 51)
  - Radio Scripts 1953-1954, n.d. (Box 51)
  - Religion - First Unitarian - Integration Committee 1963 (Box 51)
  - Religion - First Unitarian - Religious Education Committee n.d. (Box 51)
  - Religion - Miscellaneous Materials 1957-1998, n.d. (Box 52)